Snehangsu De

Data Service Executive

Strong experience and proven capacity with 2 years 7 months on escalation desk for customer query in voice and non-voice process with massive customer satisfaction and clean communication skills. 1 year and 9 months experience in Database management using SQL in small business accounts and bookkeeping services. A quick learner, adept at multitasking, and comfortable working in a time constraint environment. I was Involved in call auditing, process improvement, and training of new hires.

✓ desnehangsu@gmail.com✓ Siliguri, West Bengal✓ snehangsu-de.herokuapp.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE

in linkedin.com/in/snehangsu-de

Technical Support Executive - Data ServicesConcentrix

07/2019 - 04/2021 Bangalore

- Worked for Intuit Data Services, fixing corrupted company files for Enterprise & Premier products, fixing it with My SQL commands with a satisfaction of 89.%.
- Capable of handling system-related issues, file-related issues, debugging and small business-related accounting & bookkeeping issues.
- Worked on SQL commands (foreign keys, inner joins) to fix P/L reports, company financial reports and Sales reports.
- Creating, reading, updating raw data from broken data files to an entirely new database for the user to use.

Subject Matter Expert

Amazon

07/2018 - 03/2019 Hyderabad

- Guided and managing new hires for the Primary and Concession Abuse Prevention team. Our team passed with the year's highest passing percentage of 82%.
- Worked on MS Excel for Attendance, AUX report and Daily/Weekly performance of new hires trainees.
- Handled professional mail escalations to station and respective program team regarding process miss or customer exceptions.
- Audited "D-sat" contacts and provided daily feedback and published report with the transition and training team.

Customer Operations

Amazon

08/2016 - 06/2018 Hyderabad

- Involved in 500+ contact mining for issue codes improvement to reduce incoming contacts for Amazon Home Services (AHS).
- Discussed and analysed transaction disputes and missing cheque reports through team meetings.
- Monitoring and assigning tickets regarding payment failures and cheque cancellations.
- Proficient working in Bill Desk, Citrus Pay while assisting associates with UTR/RRN for refunds.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology JIS College of Engineering

06/2012 - 05/2016 Kolkata

• Electronics and Instrumental Engineering (Graduated-7.47).

SKILLS

github.com/snehangsude



ACHIEVEMENTS

Rs. 1,500, prize for exceptional performance during Great Indian Sale'17. (10/2017 - 01/2018)

Three (3) consecutive Gold Performer of the month and twelve (12) Silver Performer of the month.

Acknowledged by the leadership team twice for Customer Delight Stories.

PROJECTS

CAP (Concession Abuse Prevention) (04/2017 - 10/2017)

 Worked as a six (6) member pilot batch for the CAP team, working on policy improvements and reduction of concession for customers/merchants abusive trend. Being as a pilot teamwork, work ethic and quick decision making helped us in making the project a huge success.

Primary Process Improvement (11/2017 - 12/2017)

 Consulted 800+ customers with a team of four(4) for feedback on new process change. The data collected was used to minimize "Where is My Stuff" queries and launching new issue codes for a better and clear data calculation.

LANGUAGES



INTERESTS

Machine Learning Neural Networks

Exploratory Data Analysis Tableau